ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزAt last you say
we've been apart too longظآز
ظآزUnwilling, unyielding, I won't let goظآز
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
ظآزIf heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vesselظآز
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزTo grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long nightظآز
=Rise Again=
=Episode 23=
The Heavenly Dao has come.
Take Ningxue and go.
I'll face the Heavenly Dao alone.
Futile.
Defy the laws all you want,
your ending is already decided.
The Heavenly Dao?
Law?
Why must you torment Ningxue
again and again?
It's not torment. It's return.
Life must return to the universe.
That is the eternal law.
What a load of nonsense!
Her life belongs to her.
Not to Heaven. And certainly not to you.
If the Heavenly Dao wants her dead,
then you're the one I should deal with!
Ningxue!
Wubing. Catch this!
What a load of nonsense!
Her life belongs to her.
Not to Heaven. And certainly not to you.
In this life,
I'll stand with you
and fight the Heavenly Dao!
ظآزTime cuts like a blade,
severing all desireظآز
Ningxue...
ظآزIn the end,
we fall into an endless tideظآز
Ningxue...
ظآزIn the end,
we fall into an endless tideظآز
ظآزIf fate is cruel,
is there anything left?ظآز
ظآزThen let these immortal bones scatterظآز
No, Ningxue!
Ningxue, don't go!
Ningxue!
ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
Ningxue!
ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزJust to meet you again in the crowdظآز
Ten thousand years ago,
you gave everything
to protect me during seclusion.
Ten thousand years later,
even if it costs me everything,
I'll protect you.
Ningxue.
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
Did you hear me?
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
We still have a wedding to fulfill.
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزI'll fade into illusion with youظآز
ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزAt last you say
we've been apart too longظآز
ظآزUnwilling, unyielding, I won't let goظآز
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
Ningxue.
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
ظآزIf heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vesselظآز
I have one last wish.
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزTo grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long nightظآز
Su Wubing...
My Lord, can you still
feel any spiritual power at all?
If it means getting Ningxue back,
living as an ordinary person
is more than fine with me.
What a shame.
Lin Rong.
My Lord gave everything for your family.
You must repay him.
Of course.
Wubing has done so much for us.
He saved Ningxue.
We could never fully repay that debt.
Wubing, don't worry about
your spiritual power.
Come to my martial hall from now on.
I'll teach you
the Shan family's techniques.
You'll be even stronger than before.
Okay.
No way.
He's already engaged to Ningxue.
He's part of the Lin family now.
Why not?
I think he and Yingying
are a great match too.
Alright, enough.
My Lord's heart
belongs to Ningxue.
Stop arguing.
Oh, right,
where are
Ningxue and the other girls?
I already told her to come.
Why aren't they here yet?
Xiaonuan's not answering either.
And Yingying too...
Did something happen?
Look... they're here.
- Su Wubing!
Su Wubing.
You all...
Like it?
Wubing, you must choose one of us today.
That's right.
Yes.
Exactly.
ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزAt last you say
we've been apart too longظآز
ظآزUnwilling, unyielding, I won't let goظآز
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
ظآزIf heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vesselظآز
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزTo grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long nightظآز
Got it.
Thanks.
You've been asleep so long.
You haven't heard the good news.
(Against Fate)
Look, this is your script.
They loved it.
A lot of people want your autograph.
You always used to read to me.
After being asleep so long,
you've probably forgotten.
Let me read it to you now.
"Su Wubing finally married Lin Ningxue."
"At the wedding, he recalled the past."
"Fate... had finally been broken."
"But where does it all lead in the end?"
"The undercurrents in Fan City
haven't stopped."
"It looks calm on the surface,"
"but what storms still lie hidden?"